{
    "id": "93d5e7571f0d4b23b2af0631bc314a8f",
    "title": "Grammar Review Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "afb3cca202284abd85a2186d8fbf8c38",
            "title": "Grammar Review Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "I met her in Ireland ………………………",
                    "description": "We use ago with a past tense and a past time expression to count back from the present.",
                    "answers": [
                        "six months before",
                        "before six months",
                        "six months ago"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The two sisters are very much ………………………",
                    "description": "Alike means like each other.",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "alike",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have you been here ……………………..?",
                    "description": "Before is used with a perfect tense and no time expression to mean ‘at any time before now/then.’",
                    "answers": [
                        "ago",
                        "before",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "……………………….. the people were singing and dancing.",
                    "description": "All or all of can both be used before a noun with a determiner.",
                    "answers": [
                        "All",
                        "All of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I would quite like to go out, …………………….. it is a bit late.",
                    "description": "Though and although are interchangeable.",
                    "answers": [
                        "although",
                        "though",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "‘Lovely day.’ ‘Yes. Bit warm, ………………………..’",
                    "description": "Though can be used as an adverb. Although cannot be used as an adverb.",
                    "answers": [
                        "although",
                        "though",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "It is important that she ………………………… told.",
                    "description": "In American English, the structure without should is more common.",
                    "answers": [
                        "be",
                        "should be",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She looks ……………………… she is going to cry.",
                    "description": "Like is possible here in an informal style.",
                    "answers": [
                        "like",
                        "as if",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Those candies were wonderful. Could I have …………………………… one?",
                    "description": "Another can mean ‘an additional or extra’. It is used after plural nouns.",
                    "answers": [
                        "other",
                        "another",
                        "more"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Those peas were delicious. Could I have ………………………..?",
                    "description": "With plural and uncountable nouns we normally use more, not other.",
                    "answers": [
                        "another",
                        "other",
                        "some more"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I didn’t like ………………………. the movies.",
                    "description": "We use any of before a noun with a determiner.",
                    "answers": [
                        "any",
                        "any of",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Prices keep ………………………",
                    "description": "Rise means get higher/go up. Arise means begin or appear. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "rising",
                        "arising",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}